It was the Fall of 2009 and I was a professor now.
正逢2009年的秋天 我当上了教授
So I decided to change my look a little b.
所以我决定改变下穿衣风格
And pele were noticing.
这当然逃不过群众的法眼
Ah,tweed. Textile of the euch.
粗花呢 独特的布料
You know,I've always Wonded why those tweed jackets have elbow patches.
我老想知道为啥花呢夹克的手肘部位有补丁
Because the people who wear them are constantly going, "aw,geez.******
因为穿这类衣服的人老是这样 "唉 为啥没人和我嘿咻"
You are wrong. The ladies dig the profsor look.
你错啦 女人们喜欢教授的样子
You know,there is something to that.
确实这么回事
I remember thinkingmy tenth grar Was very sexy.
我记得高一时的数学老师超性感
I wonder if harold's still in jail.
我想知道Harold还在吃牢饭不
What? Tax evasion.
咋了? 逃税呗
Among otr things.
罪状之一
So guys,marshall And I wanted to invite yoto our place For a little couples'ight.
哥们姐们 我和Marshall想请你们 来家里一起过情侣之夜
Uh,sure. Why not?
好啊
For years,marshall and lily had been the only Married couple in a group full of single people
数年来 Marshall和Lily夫妻都是 一大帮光棍中唯一结婚的独苗
It got lonely.
他们寂寞了
so they were always Searching for another couple To double-date.
所以一直在寻找另一对来进行四人约会
There was only one pblem.
但唯一的问题是
- Welcome. - Gouda?
- 欢迎 - 豪德奶酪?
They sucked at it.
他们道行不够
This is grea We're having fun. You're having fun,right?
真好 我们玩得好开心 你们也是吧?
So,should w just go ahead And lock the four of usn for new year's?
那我们是不是该趁热打铁 确定下新年的四人约会?
- Um,it's apl. - Right. Sorry.
- 现在才四月份 - 对 不好意思
We're getting ahead of ourselves. Let's talk thanksgivg.
我们太超前了 那说说感恩节吧
Our parents really want to meet you!
我们的父母很想会会你们!
- Well,we suld probably be going. - Wait.
- 我们该走了 - 等下
But,wait, if you leave now, Colonel mustard just gets away with it.
等下 要是你们现在走了 就让Mustard上校逃走了
It's getting prty le. We're going to go.
很晚了 我们要走了
There's still pie.
还有派呢
Night was fantastic. We should do it again.
今晚真是太美妙了 我们该再聚次
I'm sorry,marshall, but falguni and I Are just not that into you. And you.
很抱歉 Marshall 我和Falguni不是那么喜欢你 还有你
Bujust when lily and marshall were about to give up,
但正当Lily和Marshall要金盆洗手时
Two of their best friends in the world got together.
他们两个最要好的死党走到了一块儿
And hope returned to their hearts.
他们的内心重燃了希望的火种
So when lily said...
所以Lily说...
Marshall and I wanted to invite you to our place For a litt couples' night.
我和Marshall想请你们来家里过情侣之夜
Um,surewhy not?
好啊
Barney and robin had no ide What they were about to walk into.
Barney和Robin对他们 即后的遭遇毫不知情
Okay. Game time. L's review the flow of the room.
好的 演练时间到 我们把流程再操练遍
Barn and robin enter here. Stop here for margaritas.
Barney和Robin从这进 到这里喝玛格丽塔酒
That's a great conversation starter.
这是打开话闸的绝妙机会
Wean tell them about our trip to ca.
我们可以说说我们的Cabo之旅
Great,'use I got that story about sammy har Anthe belgian waffle locked and loaded
好极了 我要说说 Sammy Hagar吃威化饼的事
Thenwe'll move on to the hot apps station.
然后气氛达到高潮
D,depending on how things are going, Some lively pre-dinner charades.
看形势发展 再来些有趣的餐前猜谜游戏
Right,but,uh, we'll play thatne by...
对 但我们要用这...
Sounds like?
听声音?
Okay,you can be robin's partner.
好吧 你能和Robin一帮
Baby,we can do this.
宝贝 必胜
- Welcome. - Gouda?
- 欢迎 - 豪德奶酪?
Meanwhile, my half-baked theory That lads dig the professor look
与此同时 实践检验了女人喜欢教授
Was actually proving to be true
这一真理的正确性
So is it har to grade papers?
批试卷难不?
No,you've just got to make it fun.
不难 你能给它加点乐趣
For exame,uh,every time I spot a grammatical error, I do a shot.
譬如说 每次我发现个语法错误 我就喝一杯
I'm trashed right now, and I blame Our public school system.
我都喝得烂醉了 我们学校的体制有问题
Sometimes thin just seem to magically fall into place.
有时 事情会奇迹般的水到渠成
So,you said you live right upstair
你说你住在楼上
Whether I's in the dating world...
不管是单对约会
Take care. Bye.
保重 拜拜
Or e double-dating world.
还是四人约会
- Nailed it! - Best nig ever!
- 成啦! - 最美妙的一晚!
Worst night ever.
最烂的一晚
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=- proudly presents
-=伊甸园美剧论坛 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=- sync:咔肉肉
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 花竹梗 葱家的小毛毛 校对: 葱家的小毛毛 Brightgrace 时间轴: 咔肉肉
How I Met Your Mother Season05 Episode04
老爸老妈浪漫史 第五季 第四集
Hey,how was the big couples' night with marshall and lily?
嘿 和Marshall Lily一起四人约会咋样?
- Brutal. - Really? How?
- 惨不忍睹 - 是吗? 怎么会?
Itas like we were on a date With a sad,chubby girl our*****
感觉就像和悲惨的我妈硬给安排的胖姑娘约会
And they were so nervous, That they weren't even making *****
他们太紧张了有时不明白他们在讲啥
Come on in. Would you like a margarita?
请进 要玛格丽塔酒吗?
In cabo,I saw sammy hagar eating a belgian waffle!
我在Cabo看见Sammy Hagar在吃威化饼
And they kept shoving platters of food in our fac.
还有他们不断地把一盆盆 吃的堆到我们面前
Let me guess: Did marshall get,like, Super intense about the cheese?
我猜猜 Marshall对奶酪过分地热情了?
Yeah,how'd you know?
嗯 你咋知道?
Poor marshal Lily's this gourmet cook, and all she lets marshall Is pick out one sad block of cese.
可怜的Marshall Lily是烹调大厨 她叫Marshall挑出一块悲伤的奶酪
That's prosciutto-wrapped melon.
这是火腿烩西瓜
You guys are going to want to get in on this gouda.
你们肯定想配点奶酪吃
That's seared scallops with a mango chutney.
这是芒果酱淋烙扇贝
Seriously,don't sleep on the gouda.
说真的 可别把奶酪留着过夜
And that's Loter ravioli in a black truffle oil.
这是黑松露菌油馄饨
Tick-tock goes the gouda clock.
配着奶酪开动吧
Um,we-we-we didn't realiz.*******
我们 我们不知道要来这吃饭
We sucked down a couple tacos outside the subway.
我们在地铁那边吃了好多墨西哥饼
P.S.,not sitting great.
饱得坐不下啦
And if anything didn't go according to plan, They would freak out.
要是遇到计划外的意外状况 他们会有些神经质
What do you mean, the egg timer is broken?
煮蛋计时器坏了是啥意思?
What are we going tose for charades,sweetie?
猜谜游戏该怎么办啊 亲爱的?
I'm working on it,darling. Okay? Just stall them.
我正在忙 亲爱的? 拖住他们
Now,robin... You work in television.
Robin...你在电视机里工作
We're experiencing some technical difficulties. You get that?
我们遇到点技术难题 你懂不?
we're still laughing. Right? Laugh,marshall.
我们还在笑 对吧? 笑 Marshall
Comen,they just got excite They've been looking for couple best friends forever.
只要他们快乐就好 他们踏破铁鞋找成对的好友好久了
Plus,I'm sure they weren't th bad.
还有 我确信他们没这么糟
Show him.
拿给他看
Is is a web site Marshall alreadyade about last night.
这是Marshall为昨晚做的网站
It's called itwasthebestnightever. Com.
叫最美妙的一晚.com
?it was the best night ever ?
*那是最美妙的一晚*
?laughter raining down like April showers ?
*欢声笑语如四月的雨般洒下*
?oh,we talked for hours...?
*我们秉烛夜谈*
- ?best night ever ? - oh,that's no good.
- *最美妙的一晚* - 不太妙
?then we played charades ?
*一起玩猜谜游戏*
?lily made some creme brulee, lay-lay-lay-lay ?
*Lily做了焦糖布丁 啦啦啦啦*
?and now that we're best couple friends ?
*我们是最好的情侣朋友*
?there's only one thing ?
*还有一事*
?left to say...?
*我要问*
?are you free?Are you free?Are you free??
*你们有空不? 有空不? 有空不?*
?are you free?Are you free next Saturday??
*你们有空不? 下周六有空不?*
- That's the th. - ?are you free??
- 就是17号 - *你们有空不?*
riday or Sunday would also work. Or basically any other day.
周五或周日都行 随便哪天都行
Needless to say, we've both changed our e-mail addresses.
当然了 我们都改了邮箱地址
I don't understand.If last night went so ibly,
我不明白 要是昨晚那么惨淡
Why do lily and marshall think it was such a hit?
为啥Lily和Marshall觉得成了呢?
I mean,we knew we were gonna ve fun tonight, But we hado idea how much.
就知道今晚会特带劲  没想到这么High
Yeah,tough luck Every Saturday night I've ever had,
先前的周六过得真没意思
'cause this one just blewou out of the water.
和今晚一比 之前的读黯然失色
- Let's do it again,sn. - Yeah,we'll call you.
- 改天再聚 - 嗯 我们会打你们电话
They're your friends! Y would you just blatantly lie to them like that?
他们是你们的朋友! 你们咋能明目张胆地骗他们?
Well,that's what you say at the end of a crappy date.
那么烂的约会结束后 你也这么说
Hey,ted. Great time last night.
嘿 Ted 昨晚真开心
Welllet's do it again,soon. At ti',uh,call you.
改天再聚 我会打你电话
right?
对吧?
- Who was at? - Oh,I n't want to brag,
- 谁啊? - 我不是卖弄
But it seems chicks are really digging The whole professor thing.
但貌似妞们真喜欢教授来
Last night, She picked me up at e bar. And then...
昨晚她在酒吧认出我来 然后...
Wellshe actually Wound up falling asleep the couch.
其实她在沙发上睡着了
But,hey,that happens.
但 嘿 总会发生这类的事情的嘛
- Uh,no,it doesn't. - Sure,it does.
- 不 不会的 - 当然会发生
You know,she was, She was just exhausted from being turned on.
她 她只是激情过后累坏了
But you heard her. She wants to do it again,soon.
但你听到啦 她说改天再做 很快哦
Ted,let me ask you a queson.
Ted 我问你
- Where doeshis girl li,exactly? - Westchester. Why?
- 这妞到底住哪? - Westchester 咋了?
You're the sexless innkeeper.
你是荒度春宵的客栈掌柜
my god! You're right! He's tally the sexless innkeeper!
我的天! 你说得对! 他绝对是荒度春宵的客栈掌柜!
What the hell is "the sexless innkeeper"?
"荒度春宵的客栈掌柜"是啥鬼东西?
Ted,many a man-- nay,many a soul--
Ted 许多男人 不 许多灵魂
Has their own tale of the sexls nkeeper.
都遭遇过荒度春宵
Why,I had run-in with one just last year.
我去年就遭遇了这种滑铁卢
I even composed a poem about it.
我还为此赋诗一首
- Would you care to hear it? - Not really.
- 你想听不? - 不想
T'was the night before new year's, And the weather grew mean.
那是新年前夕 雪虐风饕
It was 3:00 in the morning, And I was stranded in queens.
凌晨三点我困在皇后区
The tavern grew empty, Thgas lights grew m.
客栈渐渐冷清 火也慢慢暗下
The horse-drawn rriages were all but snowed in...
马车都被大雪困住
Wait. If this was last year, Why are you acting like it was oliver twist?
等下 要是去年 你咋说得像雾都孤儿?
Ted,it's a poem.
Ted 这就是诗歌
Last call was approaching, And my fortunes looked bleak.
快要打烊了 我看不见一丝希望
Then I turned to my left And stifled a shriek.
然后我往左一看 差点没叫出声
She had a peach fuzz beard And wehed 16 stone.
她满脸胡渣 重达千斤
She bbled up hot wings And allowed the bones.
她抓起辣翅 囫囵吞下
I muffled a scream And threw up in my mouth.
我强压住惊恐 从嘴中呕出
I asked,"where do you live?"
我问道"你住哪里?"
And she said, "one block sth."
她说"往南穿过一条街"
I swallowed my pride And six shots whiskey.
我放下身份 外加灌了6杯酒
And prayed to the gods That she wasn't too frisky.
祈祷上苍 她别太折腾
Back in her cave, she prepared us a snack.
回到她的老穴 她要去准备夜宵
往南穿过一条街
'neath her mightyooves, the floorboards did crack.
她的爪子踩得地板裂得嘎嘎响
But when she returned, She found a sound sleeper.
但当她回来时 只见一个熟睡的人儿
And thus she became The xless innkeeper.
因此 她成了荒度春宵的客栈掌柜
And so are you
你也是
Wait,you're saying that girl Just used me for a place to crash?
等下 你是说那妞 只是利用我找个地儿睡觉?
Ted,ou mentioned that yolive right upstairs.
Ted 你提到你就住楼上
She saw the tweed jacket which basically says You're not interested in,
她见着粗呢夹克就等于说 你没那方面兴趣
nor probably even capable of,havi sex.
或者根本是性冷淡
And she thought, "hey,free lodging."
她就想"嘿 免费住一宿"
No way. I'm not the sexlesinnkeeper.
才没有 我才不是荒度春宵的客栈掌柜呢
Ted,that girl no whad no iention Of ever hooking up with u.
Ted 那女孩从来没有打算和你上床
Which is funny, because usually It's the innkeeper who offers turndown service.
好笑的是 通常是客栈掌柜才有开床服务 (也有拒绝的意思 一语双关)
Hey,guys. Good news.
伙计们 好消息来了
First of all,you can ignore all the e-mails And texts we've sent you.
首先 你们可以忽略 我们给你们发的邮件和短信了
We have. Go on.
已经忽略了 继续说吧
Because we wen ahd and booked That couples' weekend for all of us in vermont!
我们另作安排了  为我们四个预订了在佛蒙特州的情侣周末
Wait,you guys were rious about that?
等下 你们认真的?
Oh,we never joke about b's, Especially at the height of syrup season.
我们对于家庭式旅行从来不开玩笑的  何况又是农家乐的黄金时节
Saturdaywe've got apple-picking, Antiquin then a hated hay ride.
周六我们先摘苹果 淘古董 接下去就是惊险自行车之旅
And then on Sunday, we're up at 6:00 a.M. For the fall folge hike.
然后是周日 我们6点钟起床  参加秋日远足
Now,you bettepack your long johns,'cause it is cold up there.
你们最好要准备好球衣秋裤哦  因为那边可是很冷的哟
Look!
听我说!
I'm sorry that we have been doing your calls,
很抱歉一直躲着你们的电话
But we respect you guys too much As friendso give you some song and dance.
我们很尊重你们  作为朋友我们只能客套应付下
You deserve the truth.
但是你们得知道真相
The us navy has found intelligent aln life At the bottom of t ocean.
美国海军在海洋的深处发现了 智能外星生命迹象
For reasons I can't explain,robin and I Have been tapped to lead the expedition.
出于某种原因  Robin和我被选为这次考察的负责人
Wow,barney.
喔 Barney
That kind of soundlike the stuff you say to girls When yo're too much of a coward to dump them.
这话听着怎么这么象 你没有勇气甩女生时候编的瞎话呢
Yeah. You know,that's exactly what it sounds like.
没错 听上去就是嘛
But if that's true, that's awese.
不过如果是真的话 真的很酷哦
What's going on?
到底怎么了?
Look,all th couple-y stuff, it's just not us.
这些情侣之间的事情 真的不合适我们
Barney and I are barely equipped to date each other, Let alone you guys.
Barney和我做情侣都自顾不暇了  何况还要应付你们
Plus,the alien thing.
再加上 还有外星生物的事情
- Come on,marshall. Let's go. - yeah,let's go.
- 好吧 Marshall 我们走 - 我们走
- Know what,lily... - No,you ow what?
- Lily 你... - 你们知道么?
I hope those underwater aliens are cold-bloed.
我衷心希望那些深海外星生命冷血无情
'cause then y guys will get along justine.
这样你们就能和谐了
I think they bought it.
我觉得他们相信外星人的事了!
I can't believe ey broke up wh us.
我不敢相信他们居然和我们分手了
We're so lovable.
我们这么可爱滴
No,we're not. We're ugly and gross.
不是 我们不可爱 我们丑陋而恶心
I thought we did everything right.
我以为我们进展顺利
I know! I know. We had the gouda. We had my waffle story.
就是嘛 就是吗 我们准备了豪达奶酪 还有我的威化饼的故事
I even st them a awesome photo montage.
我还给他们寄了很棒的照片剪辑呢
Nothing.
没啥
,dear god.
饿滴神啊
Marshall,we've beeover and over this.
Marshall 这事我们说了几千遍了!
You have to stop sending those to people.
你不能再寄那种东西给人家了
It was true.Marshall had become addicted to creating songs
她说的没错  Marshall痴迷于自己创作配曲
And photo montages documenting various mundane events.
然后配上无论大小场合拍下的照片剪辑
So for months, all of marshall's Iends and professional colleagues Were getting e-mails like this...
几个月来 所有Marshall的朋友和同事们 都收到了这类的邮件...
?ordered chinese food today ?
*今天点了中国菜*
?some moo shu pork sauce got away ?
*木须肉酱汁撒了些*
?flipped the cushion now everythi's okay.?
*弄脏了沙发垫  现在已经干净了*
?cat-sitting for lily's mom ?
*帮丈母娘照顾猫咪*
?cat-sitting folily's mom ?
?it's gonna be fun it's gonna brg us all closer together.?
*一定会很有趣 大家欢乐又舒畅*
?cat funeral ?
*猫咪的告别式*
?it was an accident ?
*只是个意外*
?and not entirely my fault ?
*并不全是我的错*
?cat funeral ?
*猫咪的告别式*
We'll miss you,whiskers.
*我们会想你的 Whiskers*
I can't believe yousent them on. They think we're insannow.
你怎么能寄给他们那些呢  他们准以为我们是神经病了
If I recall,they didn't mp us Until you brought up that vermont tri It was way too early.
我没有记错的话 直到你提起那个佛蒙特州的旅行时  他们才甩了我们的 那个旅行为时太早了
Rst,a boat ride around the city, Then a trip to vernt.
先要坐船环游纽约 然后再能去佛蒙特州嘛
It's a rookie mistake, and you're better thanhat.
这是菜鸟级的错误 你不该犯的
Oh,what about you forgetting To check the egg timer for charades?
你忘记检查猜谜游戏要用的煮蛋计时器 又怎么说呢?
I gave you one thing to do,marshall. One thing.
我就让你干了一件事 Marshall 就一件事你还搞砸了
One thing? One thing?
一件事? 一件事?
Really?
真的?
So,I gus that gouda Just walked itself right through the door...
那么豪达奶酪是自己走出门来...
Sliced itself up, And arranged itself in a perfect semi-circle
自己把自己切了  把自己排列成完美无缺的半圆
Around not three,not four...
包围在不是3块 也不是4块...
But five different kinds Of sturdy, cheese-bearing crackers?
而是5块不同种类的奶酪饼干上?
You're a sturdy, cheese-bearing cracker!
你就是块不开窍的奶酪饼干!
Guys,ly and marshall haven't been to the bar all week.
伙计们 Lily和Marshall一周都没有来了
They're taking th really hard.
他们把这事看得很重的
Ted,I could listen to this guilt trip all day, But don't you have to get back up to the inn?
Ted 我可以一整天都听你唠叨  但是你不得回你的客栈去咩?
I mean,who's working the front de?
谁来照管前台呀?
Seriously,they're your friends. Yogot to go apologize.
我说真的 他们是你们的朋友 你们必须道歉
To your point,ted, as an innkeeper,
如你所说 Ted 作为个开客栈的
Do you do that cheapy thing Where u only change the linens upon request?
你是不是也只在客人提要求时 才更换床单被罩?
I mean,I mean,I mean,how much water is that actually saving?
我是说 这又能省多少水啊?
Robin,you know I'm right. Ignoring aroblem doesn't make it go away.
Robin 你知道我说的是对的 无视问题并不能解决问题
Usually, it jusmakes it bigger.
只会使事态越来越严重
- You're right. - Thank you.
- 没错 - 谢谢
All that sexlessness has de you wise.
无性生活让你平添智慧了
Fogod's sake!
苍天啊!
Mint on the pillow,ted!
Ted 别忘了在枕头上放薄荷糖! (西方酒店的习俗)
- And don't charge for wi-fi. It seems greedy! - It does.
- 无线上网不许收钱 别太贪心了 - 就是嘛 (夫唱妇随的一对啊)
But eventually, Even barney and robin had to admit They owed lily and marshall an apology.
最终 即便是Barney和Robin也得承认 他们的确需要向Lily和Marshall道歉
wanted to an apsay we're sorry.
我们只想说我们很抱歉
I wish you had called.
你们该先打个电话的嘛
I swear,he was right there Just eating a belgian waffle!
我发誓 他就在那里 吃比利时威化饼!
Well,he can't have enjoyed it As much as I'm joying this gouda!
他那时候肯定没有我现在吃豪达奶酪 一样享受的!
Um,listen, Now's not a good time. We'll call you.
听着 现在时机不大好  我们会再打电话给你们的
- Wait wait. - We just want...
- 等等 - 我们只是...
Hey.guys.
伙计们
Long time no see. Have a seat.
好久不见哦 快坐呀
- Oh,we can't. We're here with py and shea. - Yeah,sorry.
- 不行 我们是和Py和Shea一起来的 - 没错 对不起咯
it's just... We haven't seen you guys all week.
但是... 我们都一个多星期没有见到你们了
Hey,maybe all six of us could hang out.
我们可以六个人一起啊
Oh,might be weird.
有点诡异哦
- We'reind of on a doub date. - Yeah.
- 我们是在四人约会 - 没错
Wouldn't want you to feel like a fifth and sixth wel.
不希望你们感觉自己是第五个和第六个轮胎 (多余的)
Who the hell are these people?
这俩到底是哪里来的啊?
They just moved here from hawaii.
他们刚从夏威夷搬来
Py is a total foodie and shea,well...
Py是个美食家 而Shea...
- She's... Shea... - Shea is just...
- 她.. Shea... - Shea完全是...
Anyhoo,we can't ay long.
我们不能久留了
We're just gonna grab a quick beer and then take these kooks For a boat ride around the city.
我们只是来拿个啤酒  然后要带他们去坐船环游纽约
Wow,it sounds like this I getting pretty serious.
听上去挺认真的嘛
Well,we don't want to jinx it,but,uh...
我们不想这么早说 但是...
We kind of think they might be the two.
我们觉得他们也许就是我们的天命天子了
- Pfft,who needs 'em? - Not us.
- 谁在乎啊? - 就是嘛
?livin' alone ?
*孤独的生活*
?we think of all the fends we've known ?
*想遍了所有的朋友*
?but when we dial the telephone ?
*当电话接通*
?nobody's home ?
*却没有人在家*
Two for dinner.
两个人的台子
Just the two of you?
就两个人?
?all by ourselves ?
*只剩下我们两个*
?don't want to be ?
?all by ourselves anymore ?
*只剩下我们两个*
?all by ourselves...?
Hey,why don't we call That weird couple down the hall from you?
我们干嘛不打电话约那对 在大厅等你的奇怪的情侣?
You know,with the ferrets?
就是穿着貂皮的那对?
Maybe they want to come over and play taboo.
也许他们愿意过来 玩taboo游戏呢 (看卡片猜词)
After midnight? No way. We can't tabooty-call them,it's paetic.
三更半夜的? 我们不能这样 打电话找人来玩游戏 太可悲了
Hey,guys.
伙计们
Barney, are you wearing sweat pants?
Barney 你穿的是运动裤?
Maybe. But they're armani.
貌似是的 但这可是阿玛尼的
Okay,guys,I've got some bad news for you.
伙计们 我有个坏消息
So I'm just going to come out and say it.
我现在打算说出来了
You're a couple.
你们俩是情侣
And no matter how hard you try to fight it, Couples need other couples.
无论你们多不想承认也好  情侣需要别的情侣一起
That's why you miss marshall and lily.
这就是为什么你们会想Marshall和Lily
And can't you just admit that?
你们不能就承认么?
oh,yeah!
太好了!
That was amazinglily!
真好玩 Lily!
I know! When I got that left-hand- yellow,I was like,"what?"
对啊! 我抽到左手黄色格的是  我就想"苍天啊?"
- U gu are the best. - Oh,right back ayou!
- 你们真好 - 你们也是!
For charades
为了猜谜游戏准备的
How do we know you two won't hurt us agai
我们怎么知道你们不会再次伤害我们?
You don't.
你们不知道
You know what?We have two very nice people up in that apartnt
知道么 我们公寓里正有两个很棒的人
Who e perfect for us.
完全合适我们
Then what are you doing, Standing out in the rain with us?
那你们为什么和我们站在雨中?
Damn it. Why there something so attractive about a bad boy... And girl?
真该死 为什么我会对一个坏男孩 还有一个坏女孩如此痴迷?
I think we can change them.
我想我们能改变他们
Come here,you two.
过来吧 你们俩
We'll neverleep on the gouda again.
我们再也不会把奶酪留过夜了
Hey,barney. Ot a little poem for you. You want to hear it?
Barney 我给你写了首诗 想听听吗?
not really.
不大想
'twas the night beforei had hours to kill.
就在昨日 闲来无事
I sat in the tavern, grading parchments with quil
闲坐酒馆 执羽阅卷
- With quill - Barney.It's a poem.
- 羽? - Barney 这是首诗
A busty,yng lassie flashed me a grin.
有个小妞 媚眼频频
Her garb sd "classy," but her eyes whispered "sin."
衣着款款 眼波流转
She said,"you're a teacher?"
她问"你是老师?"
I sa,"yes,indeed."
我答 "正是正是"
"I must have you," she moaned.
"我要你" 她呻吟道
"I'm turned on by tweed."
"你的衣服令我性奋"
With haste we did scamper To my chamber anon.
迫不及待 奔向卧室
We fell to the couch, and,bro,it was on.
倒向沙发 好戏上场
I unlaced her bodice. Our passions grew deeper.
罗衫轻解 娇喘连连
And thus ends the tale of the sless innkeeper.
这才是荒度春宵的客栈掌柜的真正结局
No way. You made that up.
什么呀 你瞎编的
Are you coming back bed,professor?
你要回床上来吗 "叫兽"?
D,I love being single.
苍天哦 单身万岁
Barneyyou ready for brunch with lily and marshall?
Barney 你准备好和Lily还有Marshall 吃早午餐了么?
What have I done?
我到底干了啥啊?